

Syed Muhammad **Saqlain**

Fullstack Developer

Contact

- +92 300 0580479
- saqlainprii @amail.co
- @saqlain1020
- (in acadain1020
- (#) https://saqlain1020.com

Skills

Frontend:

ReactJ5 (MUIS) Typescript (NextJS)
Redux Toolkit React Guery (React Reac
Framer Gsop Sscs Formik Expo
React Native Webpack/Rollup/Tsup
Socket(0)

Backend:

Node
 Express
 Firebase
 MongoDB
 SocketlO
 Rest Apis
 JWT Auth

Blockchain:

Devops:

Heroku

Vercel

Turborepo
Firebase

Rallway

AWS Beanstalls

AWS Pipeline

AWS AWS Pipeline

AWS AWS Firebase

AWS AWS Firebase

AWS Cadebuild

AWS ECG

AWS Routess

AWS Certificate Manager

AWS Cloudfront

AWS SS

AWS Charlifore Manager

Othere

About me

I'm Saqlain an ambitious problem solver with a passion for learning and implementing new solutions, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Experienced in creating logical and innovative solutions of complex problems.

My goal is to climb the ladder and become one of the leading experts in my field, and want to be a part of something bigger.

Education

2019-Current

BS:SE University of Karachi

2018

Intermediate Adamjee Govt Science College

Matriculation

Work Experience

2021 - Current

Dechains

Role: Senior Frontend Developer, I am responsible for creating whole responsive frontend of various blockshain related apps lilia NFT Markeplaces, Farming sites etc. While integrating and working on modularized custom libraries for apis, graph and blockchain communication, Libs being compiled with webpack; rollup, stup etc

2020 - 2021

Slectus (US)

Multivendor ecommerce style platform with commision support and a complex profile and product management system and realtime features, MERN Stack App. Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for all the frontend work and integrations on the platform, little backend development authorized.

2020 - 2020

Novasoft

Software House.
Role: Frontend Develop

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for most of the frontend work and integrations on their multiple projects in works.

1 Year

Al-Raheem Printing Services

Role: Graphics Designer

3rd Party Projects

Some of many third party app i have developed as a developer

NFT-Crypto web apps on ReactJS | Apple Mapkit React App

Firebase Data and Auth applications

Social Links sharing apps with NFC tag functionality

Many of my projects can be viewed on my webportfolio https://saqlain1020.com

Extras

Fiverr freelancing experience

- Certificates:-Webicamp module winner
- Graphics desiging from Arena Multimedia
- Contribution ICISCT 2020
- Envoirment Modeling Workshop participation by Comstech of OIC